[MARLA] In order for
a compound to be pure,
it has to undergo a tedious
process of removing impurities.
In organic chemistry,
we call this,
purifying organic compounds.
In life, we call it, purging?
And maybe what I am
experiencing right now
is the painful act of purging.
To rise, I have to fall first.
To be truly alive,
I have to die first.
Die?
Death?
Is this the end for me?
No.
This can't be.
Would this moron's face
be the last thing I'd see
on my last day on earth?
No!
This is just part
of the purifying process.
Which process am I in right now?
Distillation?
Crystallization?
Chromatography?
Sublimation?
Extraction?
Or...
just plain realization?
Realization that
this Cole is not the same Cole
that I fell in love
with years ago.
Maybe I was too
in love to see it.
Explain that, science!
[COLE GRUNTS]
[CRASHES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GASPS]
What are you doing here?
Marla, I'm here to apologize.
[MARLA] Apologize?
Because you hurt me?
[COLE] No!
I could never do that
to you, Marla.
So what?
I did this to myself?
[COLE] Marla,
I did everything to save you,
but I didn't get there in time.
Remember?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Marla...
I'm sorry for everything I said.
My emotions just got
the better of me.
That's why I said
those things, Marla.
I thought you were
behind that stunt
just to get back at me, right?
Marla.
Marla, you're not
the only victim here.
You're not the only one
who got hurt, Marla.
I was hurt as well.
You know that physical injury
can heal faster
compared to
my emotional feelings, Marla.
I'm a victim, too.
In fact...
I'm more of a victim than you.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing here?
- Marla, are you okay?
- Hey!
[NYX] Get out!
Marla, I'm going
to ask you again.
Are you involved with
what happened to Lester?
I said no!
But we're good.
Right?
Cole, you know, with everything
that's happening...
I need space.
I need to think.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Marla.
Space?
To think?
[APRIL] What for?
Even after what he did to you?
[NYX WHISTLES]
Shh.
Relax.
Let's not pressure Marla
just yet.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
Girls.
Be honest.
Did you do that to Lester?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARLA CLEARS THROAT]
[SCOFFS] Okay, fine.
Yes. It was us.
I knew it!
- I knew it.
- Nothing happened anyway.
Cole and Lester aren't
facing any consequences.
It's being covered up.
They reduced it as a prank.
Exactly.
They say Principal Mckenna's
hunting down everyone
who's involved with the torture
of her baby boy.
But we were all there
at the party.
I mean, stargazing.
So, I think,
we're covered by our alibis.
Alibi?
Daphne, you too?
I just learned that night,
when April talked to me.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Hi, Daphne.
[DAPHNE] Hi?
[APRIL] Oh, I have
to show you something.
Can we talk?
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Girl?
[NYX] I'm sorry,
I forgot to return this.
It was a back-up plan in case...
you didn't Agree-ana Grande.
- You scared me, girl.
- Sorry.
I kept looking for this.
You know how
I can't afford a new one.
- I'm sorry.
- [DAPHNE CLICKS TONGUE]
It's okay.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
To be honest...
I feel afraid every time...
every time I see Lester.
So he deserved it.
[DAPHNE] Somehow, at least...
we got him to admit things?
Isobel...
are you okay?
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you okay, Marla?
Yeah.
The doctor told me
there's no major injury,
so I'll be fine in
maybe a week or two.
I'm sorry.
[NYX] Girl!
- You apologized! Oh, my God!
- Okay, okay.
- Calm down, girl.
- First time.
It wasn't part of the plan
to get you hurt.
It was...
careless of me.
I'm sorry.
Why are you even apologizing?
You weren't the one who hurt me.
Cole did.
I still feel...
guilty.
[ISOBEL EXHALES SHARPLY]
[MARLA] Well, you shouldn't be.
Anyway, speaking of Cole.
He's denying everything.
[MARLA] So, I'm hoping
we have surveillance video?
Oh.
[APRIL] I kind of...
disabled all
the security cameras...
so we won't get caught.
So, we won't get any evidence.
I'm so sorry.
[DAPHNE] Damn it.
Why is it that...
we're always on the losing side?
The system is against us.
[INHALES DEEPLY] Well, girls,
better get ready for a long
and bloody fight.
[NYX] Hey! Wait!
Wait a minute.
Hold on that thought,
in the name of Beyoncé.
[NYX] Can you...
hold your bloody thought
and bloody privates as well?
Because, you know,
this might be
our special reunion!
Comeback, you know,
of the girl group?
This is it.
This is our comeback,
I can feel it!
[NYX SQUEALS]
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[SNIFFLES]
[COLE] April.
How do you like your new room?
It's great, yeah?
I think you very much
deserve it like this, April.
You monster!
What's wrong with you, Cole?!
- [EXHALES SHARPLY]
- [COLE SINISTER LAUGHTER]
What's wrong with me?!
I knew it.
You were the ones behind
what happened to Lester,
right?
And I know only Isobel
could come up
of that naughty
and cruel method.
And I know only Nyx
has the skill...
to build a machine like that.
April...
I am so close
to achieving my goals.
And nobody,
will ever get in my way.
[BOTH LAUGHING WRYLY]
Don't be so sure, Cole.
Because we will do everything...
...to bring you down.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh no, I'm scared.
I'm so afraid of you, April!
I'm so scared!
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
You see this?
Sir beat me up once again...
and threatened...
...to put me in the military.
No.
Of course...
I won't let that happen!
Why?
You deserve it!
You deserve it more.
I didn't deserve that.
Dad doesn't give a shit
about me.
Okay.
Consider this as a warning.
If I go down,
I'll make sure all of you
will go down with me.
And tell this to your
crazy friends,
that this is war.
- [GRUNTS]
- [MONITOR CLATTERS]
You are just like him.
Ba-bye.
[SLAPS]
[COLE CHUCKLES WRYLY]
[POIGNANT MUSIC PLAYING]
[SNIFFLES]
[CRIES, SOBS]
[POIGNANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SNIFFLES]
[CRYING, SOBBING]
[EXHALES, SOBBING]
[SNIFFLES]
- [POIGNANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SOBBING, SNIFFLING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[DOOR CLICKS OPEN]
Hi.
Oh, hi.
Hmm.
I brought you these.
[MARLA] Aw! Thank you.
How are you?
I'm okay.
Thank you.
Thank you for helping me.
Had I read Nyx's message
earlier,
I could have prevented this--
[MARLA] Shh.
Stop blaming yourself.
It's okay.
I'm okay.
In fact, the doctors already
gave me clearance,
I can go back to school.
Hey, can you sign my cast?
I think there's
a pen inside there.
Pink.
Yes.
Marla, I'm worried about
you and the girls.
This is a dangerous game
you're playing.
For now, this is how
you end up, but,
who knows...
Maybe next time it won't just
be minor injuries anymore.
And--
Marla, Cole is a dangerous man.
I know.
I saw all the signs,
but I chose to ignore it.
You know,
I've always judged my mom
for her poor life decisions.
Always followed her heart.
Always the heart.
And now she's slowly
dying of a broken heart,
because of a man.
I told myself,
I'd never be like her.
I'd make smarter choices.
I'd make wiser decisions
when it comes to men.
[SIGHS]
But, look at me now.
It's just one man,
and I'm already
bending all my rules.
See, even my arm got bent.
Who would have thought?
Me...
Marla Briones...
with a genius-level IQ,
would misbehave like this?
But that what separates you
from other geniuses.
You feel things deeply.
You might consider it
as weakness,
but it's a strength.
You're still human after all.
It's normal to misbehave
sometimes.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- Whatever you do--
- Hmm!
[CHUCKLES] I'm sorry.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
I'll sign it already.
[CHUCKLES]
Gently...
Make it nice.
"GWS Miss Behave, Warren."
Ouch!
Just kidding.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[COLE GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
- [CHAIR CLATTERS]
- [GRUNTS]
I don't like what happened
to Lester.
The girls outsmarted us
because of your stupidity!
[CLAPS]
I'm sorry, bro.
[SCOFFS]
I can't believe
I fell for that trap.
[SLAMS] I can't believe
I fell for that trap!
[MIGO] Bro, it's okay.
Come on.
It's not your fault that they
know your weakness.
[LESTER CHUCKLES WRYLY]
You know...
Your reconsideration appeal
to return to SOSH
is still being approved.
Do you know how lucky you are
that you're still part of
this school because of my mom?!
I could go to her right now...
[SNAPS FINGER]
You'll be gone. Huh!
- Hey, hey, hey!
- It's just a joke!
Can you stop acting
like imbeciles?
Huh?!
Lester, this is all your fault!
You're too careless.
I don't want this
to happen again, okay?
We are the superior species.
They want to ruin us!
They can't outsmart us
ever again, understood?
[LAUGHING]
[SLAPPING]
You know what?
Fuck it.
I wouldn't give a damn
retaliating to Daphne
for dumping me.
I'm done.
Okay.
Game.
Too bad,
just when it seems like I'm
getting a chance with Isobel.
[LAUGHS]
[COLE] What'd you say?
Come again?
You, dumbass!
Watch what you're saying, yeah?
I know Isobel.
She'd never like you.
You're a big baby.
That witch...
...is just manipulating you.
Okay?
Always listen to me.
Isobel is just trouble.
What?
I want to know
if you're all committed
to taking those girls down?
What?!
Answer me!
- Yes.
- [MIGO] Yes.
Game.
I want all hands on deck.
And speaking of
hands on deck...
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's welcome back
my boy,
Ant.
[MIGO CHUCKLES]
What's up?
Why are you here?
Isn't he gay?
Maybe he isn't gay anymore?
Is this okay?
[COLE] Hey, hey.
They might call us names
like sexist...
maniac...
and misogynist--
And horny!
Oh, shut the fuck up.
You're so loud!
What'd you say?
[MIGO WHIMPERS]
[COLE] Can't you just
shut your trap?
Sorry. Sorry, Cole.
I'm so sorry.
Yes, I'm so sorry.
[LESTER GRUNTS]
But at least we...
are inclusive.
- [ANT] Inclusive?
- Right?
I also want my revenge.
These girls?
I will make them pay.
Especially Nyx.
[COLE] Good.
The next battle ground will be
the upcoming science fair.
So now,
did you all read the hard copy
of the research paper
that I sent you?
Tell me.
I already read this.
I did.
[COLE] Migo?
Have you read it?
No?
It's actually magnificent.
Marla wrote all this?
She's so good.
[CHUCKLES]
[MIGO] Cole?
How did you get a copy of this?
Don't you trust me?
I managed to get
her nude photos,
what more a research paper?
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
[ANT] So, what's our plan?
What's the plan?
This.
Inside this is our whole plan.
We are going to copy
what's exactly in here.
With this, we will win
the science fair.
What if they have
[COLE] Hey!
You're always interrupting me.
Don't you worry.
I deleted all copies of this.
Even Marla has
no access to this.
Again, don't worry,
we will beat them by
Marla's own brainchild.
So, give me
all those hard copies.
We need to burn them.
Give it to me. Come on.
Hey, you. Migo.
Hey.
Hand it over!
So, let's do this, boys?
Okay.
Let's show them who really
are the Kings of SOSH.
Let's go. Yeah, go!
Whoo!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[ISOBEL] Guess what?
Someone sent a shit ton
of my nude photos at home.
Good thing my grandma
didn't see it.
[NYX] What the hell?
Who could've done this?
That's so evil of them.
[APRIL] Who else?
Cole just declared war
against us.
Did you know he smashed
every stuff I own at home?
My computers, my gadgets,
everything!
Well, since he declared war,
we'll give it.
At least, we can openly
declare war now.
[APRIL] Cole is scary.
Actually, no.
He's psychotic.
You have no idea
how low can he go.
Oh April, I know low.
And I know Cole.
He'll bring us to hell,
for sure.
He's the devil himself.
But you know what,
I was told I have
a special place in hell.
At least we're both demons.
Just a matter of
who's got bigger horns.
[DAPHNE] I know none of you
really care...
just look.
I'm Cubao's resident black belt
in street fights.
So I'd let him taste
the justice of the...
oppressed!
Hey! You're a great actress!
I love it! My turn!
I'd let him taste the justice
of the gays!
Kidding!
Okay.
We will be ready.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Ready.
I love it.
I'm tearing up.
This is it.
Oh, my God.
We are so back, back, back,
back together!
Oh, my God!
This is so fun!
I love it!
But, girls,
we shouldn't be just "ready."
Yes, I agree.
We have to strike them back...
hard.
When?
Our next battleground
will be during the Science Fair.
[APRIL] Knowing Cole, he'd
definitely show off there.
He's gonna make sure
he wins no matter what cost.
I don't know
what's got into him.
His main goal has always been
to leave this country
with a purpose.
Hey, we can't let him do that.
No, no, no, no, no.
That Science Fair will be ours.
Oh, I love it!
We'll launch our major comeback
in the Science Fair.
Oh, my God. [GIGGLES]
They won't be ready for us.
They're not ready for us!
And... speaking of ready,
I've got some tea!
[CHUCKLES]
News... flash!
Ant is back.
Yes, he's back.
What?
Why...
is Migo here?
Why is he here, too?
Well, apparently,
he sent a letter of appeal
defending
it's only a 0.5 difference
from the passing grade.
So he's desperately seeking
for reconsideration.
We can expect him to stay
because of Cole and Lester.
Is Ant gonna be a problem?
Of course not!
Don't you worry.
Don't you worry, girls!
I'll handle my nugget!
Sorry, old habit.
So hard to unlearn.
Anyway, they had
to bring Ant back
because Cole knows
that my nug-nug
is really great at
Engineering and Robotics,
right?
Alright, get lost.
I said leave!
[ISOBEL] Okay, so...
What's our project
gonna be about
for the Science Fair?
It has to be
innovative,
relevant,
groundbreaking!
Hmm...
We have to think of
something big.
'Cause I know those boys,
especially Cole.
I'm sure they're gonna try to
come up with something big.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GASPS] Woah!
My gosh, I can see it.
Science Fair will become
a bloodbath.
Bloodbath?
You got blood there, girl.
[GIGGLES]
I love it, you know.
I love it. I love it. I love it!
They are not ready for us.
But this science fair is also
very important to us.
Because guests from other
universities will be coming.
Local and international.
They're gonna be scouting
for future scholars.
You know, revenge aside,
I have been waiting for this
for so long.
Right, because we both want
to study at Harvard.
But, I hope I get
the full scholarship
'cause as you know,
my parents can't afford it.
Well, me too.
I hope with this
project of ours,
I can showcase
my mastery in Robotics.
So that it'll be so fresh
for my portfolio
when I apply to MIT.
As for me,
Harvard is not an option for me
'cause Cole's there.
But, I am eyeing for Yale.
I'll go to Oxford,
so I won't ever see you all.
But what will motivate me
the most
is to beat the boys.
- [NYX CLICKS TONGUE]
- I know, right?
But you know,
Cole has been dying
to get an internship in NASA.
- Mm?
- Hmm?
And NASA representatives
will be there
during the Science Fair.
If we can take this opportunity
away from Cole,
- that's gonna be satisfying.
- Mm-hmm.
- [ISOBEL] I agree.
- [DAPHNE] So...
how will we do that?
What's our winning project?
[DAPHNE] Marla, you're
the smartest here.
We know you're working
on a breakthrough project.
Yeah, for sure.
Ever since 2020 BC?
Before Cole.
- Come on, spill it.
- Yes, yes, yes.
I have been working on
an ongoing research,
and I'm sure,
that research is good enough
to win that Science Fair.
But...
[ISOBEL] But?
It's in my laptop.
And my laptop's got a virus.
I couldn't open any of my files.
Okay.
You do have backup files, right?
[SIGHS]
- I have.
- There, solved!
But...
But what?
- I don't have it.
- [DAPHNE] Oh.
- Oh, my god!
- Ah!
Is he like, naked?
- Nipples?
- Why is he naked?
- It's inappropriate.
- No, no, no, nothing.
It's with Cole?
- Oh, my god.
- I know those judging looks,
I know what you think of me.
I'm an idiot.
I didn't just give him a copy of
my digital but beautiful body,
but also of my brain.
[SLAPS] I'm so stupid...
[ISOBEL] It's fine.
Been there, done that.
We just have to find a way to,
I don't know,
do another project.
We're smart.
We're the SOSH's finest!
- Hey, yes, sir. Yes, sir.
- Right.
- Yes, sir. Okay!
- Of course. Amen.
Amen.
But we need to think fast,
and get to work right away
'cause all the other groups
have a headstart.
I can help!
Hey.
Is that Warren?
- Is he standing there?
- You're here?
Yeah, Isobel called me,
and asked me to help.
Who would've thought?
You got him on speed dial,
Isobel?
[PHONE RINGS, BEEPS]
Grandma?
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
[GASPS]
Hey! What happened to you?
I have an idea.
[DINGS]
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES SUSPENSEFUL]
[WHIRS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Cole...
is this vault really necessary?
It's better to be careful.
I agree,
we are super careful.
So careful that...
none of us even knows
the lock combination.
Migo,
it's just safer
that only I know.
Did you, guys,
accomplish your assignments?
Earl?
- [CRACKLES]
- [CROWD EXCLAIMS]
[WOMAN] The electricity?
Two down, boys.
Good job.
We'll surely win
the Science Fair.
Right, but,
we haven't seen what the
girls are up to yet.
- Let me handle this.
- Wait a minute,
where's Lester?
You know,
you don't have to bother
the Principal's son.
He doesn't need this.
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Cole.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC BECOMES STIRRING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
So...
Are you ready to lose, Cole?
You haven't even seen
our science project.
Well,
based on your project,
that you even locked in a vault,
I know you used
my research paper.
But you know,
for someone
who just stole the project,
you're really protective of it.
It's not even yours.
It's mine now, Marla.
[MARLA CHUCKLES]
And I'll make sure
you'll be beaten
by your own creation.
Hey, thank you.
You know what, you're right.
Because the only brain
that can beat mine...
is my own.
Believe what you
have to believe.
'Cause we're gonna win this.
Yes.
Well, you aren't wrong.
I will beat you.
I mean, myself.
You haven't seen our project.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
And...
wait 'til you see this.
Cole...
Marla,
you already know
where this is going, right?
So just quit from the
Science Fair, or else...
I don't have to say it.
You're Marla Briones.
You're smart.
[CHUCKLES]
Why are you scared?
You took a video...
of our...
Our...
Our intimacy?
S-Stop it!
Stop it.
Our lovemaking?
Our fucking?
Just wait
until I release this, Marla.
This scandal of yours, okay?
How could you?!
Oops.
You're too
full of yourself, Marla.
I'm just getting started.
All these things I do,
I do because I really want
to become top one, Marla.
Cole.
This isn't you.
Stop it.
You did this to me, Marla.
[MARLA] Stop...
Make me win the Science Fair,
or else, people will see this!
[CHUCKLES WRYLY]
Fine.
Go.
Release it.
Show everyone.
Oops.
What you did was illegal,
and I will impriso--
I don't care.
I can always claim that,
this video scandal,
is just for us, but got hacked,
and then, boom,
oh, no...
Cole,
if you have any
decency left in your body,
please, don't do this.
Okay, okay,
just relax.
Don't worry.
Marla,
when the time is right,
you'll understand that
I did all of this for us.
Don't worry, Marla.
Marla...
I still love you.
I love you very much.
I'm going crazy 'cause of you.
You drive me crazy.
But don't worry, don't worry...
everything that I do...
is for us.
Because we'll still be
together at the end.
Ah.
But for now,
you know, I need this win.
You know what
you have to do, right?
Babe?
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[MUTED] Marla?
Marla?
Girl? Are you okay?
Marla,
what happened?
Girl...
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Cole...
has a copy of our sex video...
- What?!
- What?
What the...?
You had sex...
and you recorded it?
I didn't know
that he was secretly
taking a video of us...
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
and now, he's planning
to use it against me,
to blackmail me.
[TREMBLING] He's threatening
to release our video
if we don't quit
the Science Fair.
That's too much.
I'm so sorry...
Fuck that asshole!
It's not your fault.
What do we do?
We'll quit!
We'll quit, no questions asked.
We'll quit.
Don't worry.
I'll go talk to Lester.
I'll beg for him.
I'll do everything,
I'd even get back with him,
just to get that file, okay?
Marla, I will try to hack Cole.
I'll make sure
to delete the video,
okay?
Don't worry.
It's gonna be okay.
We need a countermeasure.
We have to strike first.
If we can't win,
neither can they!
[EXHALES]
No...
We will continue...
[ISOBEL] Marla.
...and we will fight.
[DAPHNE] Marla...
Marla,
it's your sex video.
[ISOBEL] Marla,
your dignity is on the line.
My dignity
will not be tied down
to a stupid sex video.
My dignity
is in our work.
Our work.
Our dreams are on the line,
and I can't ever forgive myself
if we lose everything
because of me.
So, we will fight.
Marla,
you know this isn't right.
Trust me.
Just trust me.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[APPLAUDING]
- Go, Cole!
- Kings of SOSH!
The COVID-19 pandemic
arrived quietly...
but left a trail of grief...
...that reshaped
the world forever.
In a matter of months,
it turned ordinary life
into a fragile memory...
marked by loss...
...fear, and uncertainty.
You know,
behind every statistic was
a story of love...
heartbreak, and lives cut
painfully short...
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
...including my mother.
That's why the COVID-19 pandemic
traumatized me.
You know,
such deaths are avoidable
if we can see the hidden enemy,
which is the airborne virus.
You heard it right.
Airborne virus.
Which is why...
[MACHINE THUDS]
We developed a technology
that can detect airborne virus.
And we call this...
...the "Virus Detector."
[APPLAUDING]
Woo!
[COLE] Plus, this technology
will prevent
another worldwide pandemic!
- Yeah!
- One more!
[APPLAUDING]
We are already
at the finishing stages
of early development,
and we can assure you
that we are more than ready
for it to be studied
and further tested
by world-class scientists.
But don't take our word for it.
Let's try out the machine!
[COLE] This technology
can detect existing virus
and potentially
new virus strains.
We will try to test
the air in the area,
and we will be releasing
inactivated virus
that the machine can detect.
Are you guys ready?
- Yes, ready!
- Yeah, we're ready!
[APPLAUDING]
- Wow!
- Woo!
[MACHINE BEEPS]
- [ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
- [CROWD EXCLAIMING]
What happened, Cole?
-[MAN] What happened?
- [ANT] Migo!
[ISOBEL APPLAUDING]
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [ANT] What happened?
- [COLE CHUCKLING]
Don't worry, guys.
Don't worry.
A great man of science...
...always has backup.
Migo, take this out.
[ANT] Backup?
- [METAL DOOR OPENS]
- [COLE] Oh.
- Hey!
- Yeah.
Migo!
[MIGO] Wait. Yeah, ha-ha!
[COLE GROANS]
Okay.
- [MACHINE THUDS SOFTLY]
- Thank you.
Hoo!
For real this time.
Okay, guys!
[MACHINE BEEPING, WHIRRING]
[ANT EXHALES]
Good job.
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
This project was born
from a simple
and urgent realization.
People living with dementia
aren't just losing
their memories.
They're losing connection...
...dignity, and independence.
Inspired by
their daily struggles,
we set out to create a solution
that helps restore clarity,
strengthens human connection,
and supports caregivers.
Today,
we present not just an idea...
...but a step
toward giving back memory,
identity and hope
to the people
who need it the most.
This is Project Helen...
...named after
our groupmate's grandmother
who has dementia.
[DEVICE RUSTLING]
[MACHINE WHIRRING]
Project Helen is a technology
designed to help people
living with dementia
independently carry out
their daily tasks
in a safe, supportive,
and non-stigmatizing way,
while adapting
to their evolving needs.
It is a wearable device
that provides intuitive
communication assistance,
while keeping
its users connected,
and giving them
their independence.
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[DEVICES THUDDING]
[ISOBEL] Marla, are you okay?
[MARLA WHIMPERING]
[NYX] Marla?
[MARLA WHIMPERING,
BREATHING SHAKILY]
It's okay.
[CROWD MURMURING]
[ISOBEL] Marla.
[MARLA WHIMPERING,
BREATHING SHAKILY]
[BATS RATTLING]
- [BATS RATTLING]
- [MARLA WHIMPERING]
[MUSIC TURNS GENTLE]
What's this for?
[ISOBEL] Marla.
We can win the Science Fair
next time.
[DAPHNE]
You're more important...
...than whatever dream there is.
[DAPHNE SNIFFLES]
We're all in this together.
[NYX] Girl.
We're smart.
We can always...
...think of other ways.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
We're even now, alright?
[MARLA SNIFFLES]
You're gonna be fine.
- Cheers.
[BATS THUD]
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MARLA SNIFFLING,
BREATHING SHAKILY]
[MARLA EXHALES SHAKILY]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OBJECTS SMASH]